<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-01-26T18:00:26-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title>Ashlee</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><author><name>Ashlee Grady</name><email>ashgrady9@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title>An Ambitious, Motivated Woman// Coffee Lover// Health and Fitness Enthusiast</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/02/17/curabitur.markdown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="An Ambitious, Motivated Woman// Coffee Lover// Health and Fitness Enthusiast" /><published>2015-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2015-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/02/17/curabitur.markdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/02/17/curabitur.markdown/">&lt;p&gt;Hi, my name is Ashlee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an Informatics, Business, and Computer Science Student at Indiana University. I am passionate about the intersection of technology, fitness, and innovation as a vehicle to both change lives and empower people everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I am an enthusiastic, results-driven, team-oriented individual, I aspire to be apart of a competitive and collaborative environment that uses the power of innovative collaboration to drive success.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ashlee Grady</name><email>ashgrady9@gmail.com</email></author><summary>Hi, my name is Ashlee.</summary></entry><entry><title>Suspendisse pellentesque</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/update/2015/02/06/welcome-to-jekyll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Suspendisse pellentesque" /><published>2015-02-06T09:37:44-05:00</published><updated>2015-02-06T09:37:44-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/update/2015/02/06/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/update/2015/02/06/welcome-to-jekyll/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/01.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt; Suspendisse pellentesque mollis turpis, vitae ullamcorper arcu sagittis in. Pellentesque viverra, diam vel ultrices lobortis, urna diam efficitur diam, non ultricies enim massa et neque. Mauris lacinia purus nibh, ac consequat mi molestie ac. Suspendisse at sapien ac magna posuere imperdiet eget id nisi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nulla facilisi. Pellentesque id magna eu sapien consectetur pulvinar nec eget massa. Nunc ut volutpat felis. Vestibulum pharetra ligula vel mattis aliquam. Etiam tempor vitae nulla nec euismod. Vivamus eget justo libero. Curabitur dictum, turpis vel porttitor semper, elit turpis vehicula nibh, quis mollis metus tortor at magna.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maecenas posuere sodales magna id tincidunt. Nunc sapien ipsum, efficitur et mauris nec, tristique gravida leo. Donec at bibendum lectus, sit amet fringilla risus. Donec et justo mi. In risus risus, faucibus eget eros eget, tincidunt posuere purus. Maecenas porta lacus metus, nec varius enim egestas ac. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Nullam a nisi nulla. Nam vel varius enim, sit amet fringilla massa. Proin vel aliquam felis, quis scelerisque arcu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sed consequat mi id malesuada efficitur. Vestibulum efficitur tortor ut dictum porta. Morbi dapibus viverra risus, et laoreet lorem commodo et. Donec hendrerit posuere magna a efficitur. Nullam euismod eget nulla eget iaculis. Donec porttitor faucibus porta. Morbi et risus dolor. Mauris venenatis sem id neque hendrerit ultrices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ashlee Grady</name><email>ashgrady9@gmail.com</email></author><summary>Suspendisse pellentesque mollis turpis, vitae ullamcorper arcu sagittis in. Pellentesque viverra, diam vel ultrices lobortis, urna diam efficitur diam, non ultricies enim massa et neque. Mauris lacinia purus nibh, ac consequat mi molestie ac. Suspendisse at sapien ac magna posuere imperdiet eget id nisi.</summary></entry><entry><title>Lorem</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/01/30/Lorem/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lorem" /><published>2015-01-30T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2015-01-30T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/01/30/Lorem</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/01/30/Lorem/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/01.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt; Here is a description.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, my name is Ashlee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is kinda nice when you get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ashlee Grady</name><email>ashgrady9@gmail.com</email></author><summary>Here is a description.</summary></entry></feed>
